[{"answer": "Peace cannot be imposed on the parties.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "And with the eyes of the world on the U.N. tonight, are Israel and the Palestinians getting closer to a deal?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "What I'm saying is, to employee the people.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "And how two presidents and a top fashion designer are working to rebuild a devastated nation?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Well, there's a tremendous show of force here.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What is your feeling about what may be going on?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "It's a problematic case.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "But tell me this from a legal point of view, when you studied everything to do with this case, what's your feeling about the original conviction of Troy Davis?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Indeed it is a very difficult time.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What is the latest that's going on?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, I think that both would be grounds for halting an execution.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Do you believe that he's 100 percent innocent or do you simply believe there is enough doubt about the evidence that led to his conviction that should prevent an execution taking place?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I do know that on the last time he received an execution warrant, he refused his last meal.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "And I mean, do you know in terms of the practicalities of his evening, had he had his last meal and was he prepared for execution?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, as a Christian, as a man of faith, and because I believe of what -- because I believe in the best of America I am opposed to the death penalty.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Can I ask you, do you believe the death penalty is ever acceptable under any circumstances?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, of course they were completely overjoyed by the perspective that finally this was all over.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "What's their mood been like?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yes, they seemed -- they seemed well.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Have they had to have any kind of medical treatment so far?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, these are the kind of things that I don't really want to speak upon the -- you know, the details of the release.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Is that correct?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, you'll probably have to ask them yourself.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Do they -- do they understand that they may have done that even if it was inadvertent?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "This was a very, very important for them.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "How important was it to the two young men that their families were so determined to get them back and obviously tried everything they could to do that?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, the President Abbas met with President Obama this evening and they exchanged views about the Palestinian decision to go to the United Nations to seek full membership at the international organization.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What is your understanding of how the meeting went with Mahmoud Abbas and the president?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, actually what we are trying to achieve, we're trying to send a clear message to the international community that the current status quo that exist on the ground in the occupied Palestinian territories cannot continue.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What do you really hope to achieve this week if you can?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, I think this is an issue that has been brought over and over again by Israel unfortunately to be used as a pretext not to move forward.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How can you deliver a peace process if you don't have Hamas with you?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you are talking about from now until Friday that the Palestinian decision is very clear.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Do you sense that there's enough international world led by Barack Obama to get this done?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Well, we have indicated that the day after we become a member of the United Nations, we will engage the Israelis in negotiations in order to resolve all the outstanding issues.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Could you do that?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I hope we're going to do it by, first of all, placing the future ahead of the present which is to say matching long-term means with ends.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "How are you going to keep the republic?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a little overstated.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, it didn't sound as big as it used to now that we're running $1.4 trillion every year.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "A trillion dollars on wars?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I take the responsibility for often what I think are the best answers.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Some of the answers?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Statistically if you were to repeal the tax cuts you'd solve less than 10 percent of the problem we have today.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "And where would you put it?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, that's a different question.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "You wouldn't honestly look me in the eye and say that only 10 percent of the financial problems America has today are down to the Republicans, would you?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes, well, I have found in -- we have found in our state -- and I had to learn this the hard way, honestly -- that if you're interested in results, then you must always strive to bring people together.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What is your message to them as they continue to tear into Obama and make it all very partisan?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I believe there are circumstances in which it is warranted.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "But do you personally believe in the death penalty?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "This is certainly what juries appear to be doing.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "If there can ever be doubt, why have it?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I'm not flirting with anything.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Any truth in this theory?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Yeah I have zero intention and zero expectation.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Do you have absolutely zero intention of ever being vice president?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's something that a person ought not say.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "If somebody asked you to be, would you say no?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I can't tell you the answer to that.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Would you say no if one of them asked you?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, the first advice I would give the people of Haiti and the leadership in Haiti is not to despair and fear that they can't overcome the kinds of problems, however insurmountable they may seem.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "When you see what's happening in Haiti and the problems they've had, obviously caused by a very different natural disaster in their case, what advice would you give them about how you rebuild a country that's been through devastation?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "That is helpful at the beginning mainly, when there is this kind of situation of emergency, where all kinds of help is needed.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "How important was the direct help from the United Nations?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "First of all, I must tell you we were really caught by surprise, for not having the culture of dealing with earthquake, first, and secondly, way before the earthquake, we had no infrastructure.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "And how much more should the international community now be doing that perhaps they stopped doing?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, that's exactly the point.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "How much of that has been either wasted or, you know, lost through corruption or all the things that tend to happen in such a situation?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "If I could mention the imperative, what's always right in front of you.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "From what you've seen in Haiti, what is the imperative now?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "These are horn bracelets.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "You know, it's not as easy as I thought.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "How are they responding to this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "First of all, the Rwanda model is a model that we are following very closely.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "It is a racist thing.", "docId": "110921pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "But is that necessarily a racist thing?", "qSentId": 559}]